(Bernadette:)Well, we don't exactly.
(Bernadette:)I'm a microbiologist
for the research team.
(Beverly:)Oh, what are you
currently developing?
(Bernadette:)Some exciting new
anti-anxiety drugs.
(Beverly:)That's interesting.
(Beverly:)I just attended a lecture
on pediatric anxiety.
(Amy:)Oh, was it, uh,
Dr. Jenofski?
(Amy:)I just saw
his TED Talk!
BEVERLY:
It was.
(Bernadette:)Let's get back to Penny.
(Bernadette:)Hey, weren't you telling me
(Bernadette:)something great
about your company car?
(Penny:)Um...
(clears her throat)
(Penny:)It has seat warmers.
(knocking at door)
SHELDON:
Amy! Amy!
Amy!
Come in.
(Sheldon:)Hello, everyone.
Oh, Beverly, good to see you!
(Sheldon:)I'd love to chat,
but there's a line
(Sheldon:)that could start moving
any minute, so let's do this.
(Sheldon:)Amy?
(Sheldon:)A proper apology
requires three steps.
(Sheldon:)Step one...
an admission of wrongdoing.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I was wrong.
Step two...
(Sheldon:)a promise never
to repeat said action.
(Sheldon:)Amy, that action will never be
repeated, and that's a promise.
(Sheldon:)Step three... an earnest request
for forgiveness.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I hope you can forgive me.
(Sheldon:)And I hope you
do it right now,
(Sheldon:)'cause there's an Uber
waiting downstairs,
(Sheldon:)and I don't want to repeat
this apology nonsense